# Maarif Ur Rehman

•••• Front-End Developer /
Software Engineering Student



### **ABOUT ME**

Co-founder of UserCentral, a startup specializing in IT services and consulting in Dubai and Karachi. Overseeing a hybrid workplace focused on adaptability and creativity, I drive business development, establish growth-oriented collaborations, and implement BPO solutions. Skilled in delivering web applications, web services, and graphic design projects using React, NextJS, Python on Django, Linux, Kubernetes, and Git.

Currently pursuing a BTEC International Level 3 Foundation Diploma in Information Technology at DeMont Institute of Management & Technology, with a focus on problem-solving applications, networking, and automation. Acquired certifications in API testing and Git fundamentals, enhancing skills in web development and cloud computing.



+971 56 354 1032



syedmaarifkazim@gmail.com



55 Street, Silicon Heights 1, DSO, Dubai, UAE

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## JavaScript Scripting & Debugging as Freelance

Nov 2022 - May 2023

Meticulously inspected and fixed any potential errors, vulnerabilities, or malicious code in the codebase to ensure smooth and secure website operations for users.

### **Brand Identity Design as Freelance** 2019 - 2021

Delivered unique and visually appealing logos, banners, stationary designs, and user interfaces to effectively communicate the brand's message and values to its target audience.

### **EDUCATION**

BTEC Foundation IT at DeMont Institute of Management & Technology, Dubai

Oct 2023 - Current

*GCE O'Levels* at Cambridge International Apr 2021 - May 2023

*Primary*, School of Knowledge, Sharjah 2006 - 2015

HTML CSS JavaScript ReactJS

VCS (Git) Webpack